(Raj:)Really? What was I doing to your neck
Iast night while you were playing Xbox?
Guys, I am Iiving in a dictatorship.
"You must take a vacation.
You must have fun. You must enjoy life."
(Howard:)I don't think you have a good handle
on dictatorships.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, everybody takes vacations.
(Sheldon:)One time, they tried
to make Richard Feynman take a vacation.
(Sheldon:)But he chose instead to expand his mind
and learn something new.
(Sheldon:)He went to work
in his friend's biology lab.
(Sheldon:)Richard Feynman
was a famous American physicist...
(Sheldon:)...part of the Manhattan Project.
(Howard:)Everyone in the world of science
knows who Richard Feynman was.
Yeah, now you do too.
Oh. I have a brilliant idea.
Amy's a biologist. I'll go work in her lab.
(Howard:)Isn't that just Feynman's idea?
(Sheldon:)Ten seconds ago you never heard
of him, now you're an expert.
(Penny:)- Hey.
- Hey, you.
(Leonard:)That your laundry?
You have six things in there.